[{"question": " you can say that again mac.", "answer": " well, i couldn&#146;t have done it without you buddy. you&#146;re a genius.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " it&#146;s your mommy. it&#146;s your mommy.", "answer": " ohhhh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " that&#146;s nice.", "answer": "  mom, so what did you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " well that was umm&#133;okay.", "answer": " it wasn&#146;t the best.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " that was one of the worse things ever. and not just on tv.", "answer": " wh-what are we gonna tell him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " well, the lighting was okay.", "answer": " ohh no you don&#146;t! you got lighting last time, lighting is mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " and i have costumes.", "answer": " oh great! that means i&#146;m stuck with, &quot;so, we were watching you in there  and you were sittin&#146; right here! whoa!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " what are you gonna do pheebs?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know. i don&#146;t know. i can&#146;t lie to him again. oh no i&#151;no! i&#146;m just gonna press my breasts up against him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " and say nothing?", "answer": " uh-huh, yeah that&#146;s right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " phoebe, do you think that your favorite animal says much about you?", "answer": " what? you mean behind my back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  oh! hi you guys, oh my god! you&#146;ll never gonna believe happened to me today! i am sitting in my office and&#133;", "answer": "  you guys! you guys! you&#146;re not gonna believe what my agent just told me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " joey! kinda in the middle of a story here!", "answer": " ooh, sorry. sorry. you finish, go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " okay, so anyway i&#146;m sittin&#146; in my office and guess who walks", "answer": " i&#146;m gonna be on two tv shows! monica and phoebe: oh, that&#146;s great!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " joey!", "answer": " oh, you weren&#146;t finished?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " yeah! guess who walks into my office is the end of my story.  it was ralph lauren!  ralph lauren walked into my office!", "answer": " uh rach, if you&#146;re gonna start another story, at least let me finish mine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " it&#146;s the same story.", "answer": "  wow, it&#146;s really long.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  anyway, ralph just came in to tell me that he&#146;s so happy with my work that he wants me to be the new merchandising manager for polo retail.", "answer": " still get a discount on wedding dresses?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " i&#146;m so happy for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " well, these really are the days of our lives.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " well, since you ask. they want me back on days of our lives!", "answer": "  oh god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " i got&#151;i get a big pay raise!", "answer": " oh hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " i&#146;ll be playing drake remoray&#146;s twin brother, stryker!", "answer": " oooh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " i get to hire my own assistant! monica and phoebe: ahhh!!", "answer": "  well&#151;i got a head rush from standing up to fast right there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  and you were at this job for four years?", "answer": " that&#146;s right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " okay, well this is all very impressive hilda, um i just have one last question for you. uh, how did i do? was this okay?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i&#146;ve never interviewed anyone before. i&#146;ve actually never had anyone work for me before. although when i was a kid, we did have a maid, but this is-this isn&#146;t the same thing.", "answer": " no dear. it&#146;s not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " no. yeah, and i know that. all right, well thank you so much for coming in it was nice to meet you.", "answer": " thank you! good meeting you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " hello?", "answer": "  wow! h-umm! hi! yes, uh i&#146;m sorry the models are actually down the hall.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " actually, i&#146;m here about the assistant job.", "answer": " really?!  okay well then, all right, well just have a seat there. umm, so what&#146;s&#151;what is&#151;what&#146;s your name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " tag jones.", "answer": " uh-huh, go on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " that&#146;s it. that&#146;s my whole name.", "answer": " that&#146;s your whole name, okay of course it is! okay, well let&#146;s-let&#146;s just have a look-see here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " i know i haven&#146;t worked in an office before, and i really don&#146;t have a lot of experience, but uh&#133;", "answer": " oh come on, what are you talking about? you&#146;ve got three years painting houses. two whole summers at t.g.i. friday&#146;s, come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " it&#146;s lame, i know. but i&#146;m a goal-oriented person, very eager to learn&#133;", "answer": " okay, hold on just a second.  i&#146;m sorry, it&#146;s for human resources, everybody has to do it. could you just stand up please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": "  anyway, i should go. okay, bye.", "answer": "  hey sweetie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " hi sweetie. so, what was with all the whispering?", "answer": " i can&#146;t tell you. it&#146;s a secret.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " secret? married people aren&#146;t supposed to have secrets between one another. we have too much love and respect for one another.", "answer": " awww.  but still no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " no i&#146;m serious, we should tell each other everything. i do not have any secrets from you.", "answer": " really? okay, so why don&#146;t you tell me what happened to ross junior year at disneyland?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " oh no-no, i can&#146;t do that.", "answer": " if you tell me, i&#146;ll tell you what phoebe said.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " so, ross and i are going to disneyland and we stop at this restaurant for tacos. and when i say restaurant, i mean a guy, a hibachi, and the trunk of his car. so ross has about 10 tacos. and anyway, we&#146;re on space mountain and ross starts to feel a little iffy.", "answer": " oh my god. he threw up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " no, he visited a little town south of throw up.  so what was phoebe&#146;s secret?", "answer": " oh, nancy thompson from phoebe&#146;s old massage place is getting fired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " that&#146;s it?! i gave up my disneyland story for that?", "answer": " that&#146;s right! you lose sucker!!  please still marry me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " chandler, you have an assistant right?", "answer": "  did she call? you-you told her i was sick right? always tell her i am sick!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " no, i-i just don&#146;t know how you decide who to hire. i mean i&#146;ve got it narrowed down to two people. one of them has great references and a lot of experience and then there&#146;s this guy&#133;", "answer": " what about him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i love him. he&#146;s so pretty i wanna cry! i don&#146;t know what to do. tell me what to do.", "answer": " come on you know what to do! you hire the first one! you don&#146;t hire an assistant because they&#146;re cute, you hire them because they&#146;re qualified.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " uh-huh. no, i hear what you&#146;re saying and-and-and that makes a lot of sense but can i just say one more thing?  look how pretty!", "answer": " let&#146;s see.  oh my god! oh&#133; but no! no! you can&#146;t-you can&#146;t hire him, because that&#151;it&#146;s not professional. umm, this is for me  yes? thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " okay you&#146;re right. i&#146;ll hire hilda tomorrow. dumb old perfect for the job hilda!", "answer": " let me see this guy.  w-h-wow! don&#146;t show this to monica! and don&#146;t tell her about the w-h-wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " hey-hey-hey joey!", "answer": " hey terry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " good to see you again!", "answer": " it&#146;s been a while, huh? wow, it&#146;s funny these halls look smaller then they used to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " it&#146;s a different building.", "answer": " so! stryker remoray huh? when do you want me to start?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " why don&#146;t we start right now!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  audition? i thought you were gonna offer me the part.", "answer": " why would you think that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " well, i was dr. drake remoray, stryker&#146;s twin brother. i mean, who looks more me than me right?", "answer": " everybody has to audition.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " y&#146;know terry, i-i don&#146;t really need to do this. i got my own cable tv series,  with a robot.", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry joey that&#146;s&#133;that&#146;s the way it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " hi! tag. what are you doing here?", "answer": " i just wanted to come by and thank you for not laughing in my face yesterday. and i noticed there aren&#146;t any plants in your office so i wanted to bring you your first&#133;  there is a plant in your office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " kinda.", "answer": " right. so i guess i shouldn&#146;t put good at noticing stuff on my resume.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " oh-ohh, thank you.", "answer": " anyway, i&#146;m guessing you hired somebody.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " well&#133;", "answer": " gotcha. thanks again for meeting with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " but i hired you!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " yeah! you-you got the job! you&#146;re my new assistant!", "answer": " i am?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " i can&#146;t believe it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey! good, you&#146;re home!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " oh it&#146;s always nicer to here than, &quot;aw crap! you again!&quot;", "answer": " hey baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " i made you a surprise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " oh yeah?", "answer": " yeah, tacos! ever since you told me that story i&#146;ve had such a craving for them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " did you not understand the story?", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " hey! what&#146;s up?", "answer": " ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh, nothin&#146; much. just trying to figure out what i&#146;m gonna do for dinner.", "answer": " huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  hey&#151;ooh! what&#146;s-what&#146;s that, dinner stuff? you making dinner?", "answer": " no!  shhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " what you got over there? tacos?", "answer": " no! no. they&#146;re umm&#133; they&#146;re just uh&#133;ground beef smileys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " uhh, those are tacos.", "answer": " excuse me mr. mexico.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " eh, either way i&#146;ll pass.  i still can&#146;t eat those.  what&#146;s so funny?!", "answer": "  i&#146;m not laughing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": "  you told her!", "answer": " nancy thompson&#146;s getting fired!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  look, okay-okay i had food poisoning! it&#146;s not like i choose to do it! it&#146;s not like&#151;it&#146;s not like i said, &quot;umm, what would make this ride more fun?!&quot;", "answer": " you&#146;re right. i mean i&#146;m sorry. yeah, i shouldn&#146;t be laughing. i should be laying down papers for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "  how could you tell her?!", "answer": " i had too okay?! we&#146;re getting married! married couples can&#146;t keep secrets from one another!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh really? well i-i guess monica should know about atlantic city.", "answer": " du-ude!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  what happened in atlantic city?!", "answer": " well, chandler and i are in a bar&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " did you not hear me say, &quot;du-ude?!&quot;", "answer": " and this girl is making eyes at chandler, okay? so after awhile he-he goes over to her and uh, after a minute or two, i see them kissing. now, i know what you&#146;re thinking, chandler&#146;s not the type of guy who just goes to bars and makes out with girls, and you&#146;re right, chandler&#146;s not the type of guy who just goes to bars and makes out with&#133;girls.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": "  you kissed a guy?!! oh my god.", "answer": " in my defense, it was dark and he was a very pretty guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh mon, i laughed so hard&#133;", "answer": " ho-ho, so hard we had to throw out your underwear again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " hey&#151;ooh, how&#146;s hilda? is she working out?", "answer": " ohh, my new assistant is working out, yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " was she happy you gave her the job?", "answer": " oh, my-my new assistant has very happy that i hired my new assistant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  hello?  oh hey! can you, can you hang on a second?  it&#146;s the producers over at mac and c.h.e.e.s.e. can you excuse me for a minute?  hey, funny you should call. i was just looking over next week&#146;s script.  canceled?!  like they&#146;re taking it off the air?  ohh.  all right, see you monday.  we&#146;re not even shootin&#146; them anymore?!!  all right, bye!  they canceled mac and c.h.e.e.s.e!", "answer": " sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry joey.", "answer": " why would they do that?! it was a good show right?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " you wanna tell secrets?! okay! okay! in college, ross used to wear leg warmers!", "answer": " all right! all right! chandler entered a vanilla ice look-a-like contest and won!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " ross came in forth and cried!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " oh, is that funny?! oh, you-you find that funny?! well maybe chandler should know some of your secrets too!", "answer": " i-i already told him everything!  you shush!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " once monica was sent to her room without dinner, so she ate the macaroni off a jewelry box she&#146;d made.", "answer": " ross used to stay up every saturday night to watch golden girls!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " monica couldn&#146;t tell time &#145;til she was 13!", "answer": " it&#146;s hard for some people!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": "  of course it is.  wow&#151;whoa!", "answer": " chandler one time wore my underwear to work!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " hey!!!", "answer": " ohh, i&#146;m sorry i couldn&#146;t think of anymore for ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " ohh! ohh! in college, chandler got drunk and slept with the lady who cleaned our dorm!", "answer": " that was you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " how could this happen to me?! yesterday i had two tv shows! today, i got nothin&#146;!", "answer": " well wait a minute, what happened to days of our lives?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " uh, well they might be a little mad at me over there.", "answer": " what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " well maybe i got a little upset and maybe i told them where they could go.", "answer": " joey, why would you do that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " because they wanted me to audition!", "answer": " you! an actor?! that&#146;s madness!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " tag?  hi, who was that?", "answer": "  nobody. i was just practicing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi! rachel green&#146;s office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " you must be hilda.", "answer": " yeah, this is tag. tag, this is phoebe. phoebe, can i see you for a second?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " phoebe! that&#146;s a great name.", "answer": " oh, you like that? you should hear my phone number.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " so you hired yourself a little treat did ya?", "answer": " all right i know, i know how it looks pheebs, but i&#146;m telling you&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " but-but you know you cannot get involved with your assistant.", "answer": " yes, i know that. i know that. and i know that hiring him was probably not the smartest thing that i&#146;ve ever done. but i&#146;m telling you, from this moment on i swear this is strictly professional.  yes? (kathy enters", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " hey rachel!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " cute assistant! what&#146;s his story? is he&#133;", "answer": " gay? yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " hey! terry.", "answer": " joey tribbiani! i&#146;m surprised your big head could fit through our small halls!  i gotta go joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " wait! terry! wait&#151;look&#151;wait i-i&#133; look, i&#146;m really sorry about before. i was an idiot thinking i&#146;m too big to audition for you. you gotta give me another chance.", "answer": " i can&#146;t help you joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " this poor guy&#146;s been in a coma for five years. it&#146;s hopeless.", "answer": " it&#146;s not hopeless! dr. stryker remoray&#146;s a miracle worker. look, here he comes.  dr. stryker remoray: good morning.  drake, it&#146;s your brother stryker. can you hear me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " and cut!", "answer": "  i&#146;m back baby! ha-ha-ha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " y&#146;know, in my defense, umm there was no glitter on the macaroni and very little glue.", "answer": " and in my defense, the cleaning lady came on to me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  you have no trouble telling time now right?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " y&#146;know when i said that because we&#146;re getting married that we should share everything and not have any secrets?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " yeah that was stupid. let&#146;s not do that.", "answer": " ohh, absolutely.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " and! we should keep all the stuff uh, we told each other secret from everybody else.", "answer": " yeah, definitely!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " okay,  if you&#146;ll excuse me, i-i&#146;m gonna go hang out with some people who don&#146;t know the space mountain story.", "answer": " then, i&#146;d steer clear of phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " do you have a minute?", "answer": " well yeah, sure, what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " i got asked out twice today when i was at lunch&#133;by guys.", "answer": " oh really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " yeah. did you tell someone that i was gay?", "answer": " oh, did you not want people to know that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " but i&#146;m not gay. and i especially wouldn&#146;t want you to think i was gay.", "answer": " why&#146;s that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " i don&#146;t think i should say.", "answer": " ohh, you can say. come on, i don&#146;t want you to feel like you can&#146;t tell me things.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " &#145;kay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " well&#133;", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " i&#146;d love to ask out your friend phoebe.", "answer": "  yeah, she&#146;s gay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}]